He is fucking your mom, wtf
Uh-oh..
It is difficult.
I'm mute, i am puff the first time in my life but i am puff
I feel like a little cock.
*Jack cough*
It smells...
Smells
Incredibly much sweat.
Okay, we're getting started
We start 5 youtubers, 10 problems now we run woho !!
Ouch
Okay so hello Antonija's channel.
*Stretches*
Hello on you all.
Hello my name is anis, I'm still baking from midsummer, I hope you are doing well.
The first problem we will solve now.
*Filip reads the problem*
*Jasse reads the problem*
*Jack reads the problem*
First, if they are naughty then drop them, throw them.
Secondly, how are you interested in 2 at the same time old man ...
Can you decide on one and after you have decided who you are interested in, throw him and his friend too.
First of all, I never think you should take shit from someone.
If you become uncomfortable about something that another person tells you, I think you should say away and put your foot down.
Although it can be hard, I definitely think you should do it.
You should always tell if you feel that you are being treated badly and if you see someone else who you think is badly treated then you should also say.
Throw them how can you be interested in someone who says: "No one likes you"?
You have to respect yourself and others have to respect yourself.
You may stop hanging out with these guys and finding friends who respect you for who you are and like you for who you are.
And that is not awkward to you.
And say as it is, say this way: "You treat me like this and I don't think it's okay, I'm sorry for it"
It's okay to dare to say.
If you still find it fun to hang out with these guys, I would tell them: "could you stop making such comments"
Otherwise, unfortunately I have to stop hanging out with you.
Oh what fun I am.
This can go to hell the sickest thing I read.
*Filip reads the problem*
He sends private pictures to her.
-—-—-
"But I love him what should I do"
WTF
Ehhh ...
Either you let him and your mom flee the country and live the flea.
No, but really ask him to go to hell.
This is totally sick.
Your mom is even snapper like ... so ...
This situation is fucked.
Dump him fast as hell.
You my psychologist her name is Gunilla and I send her number to you so you can, your mom and your guy call her she is actually damn good.
So no, no, no, no.
Stop loving him, talk to your mom and say, “Mom what fuck are you doing”
You have to talk to both and then say that you don't think it's okay and say away.
This is so damn bad as it is the same snoop for two generations, I can't.
I'm so sorry i can't help you, someone else may take this one
Hello hello I give up someone else may take this one.
Seriously, Leave Him, ASAP
It is a difficult situation.
Very unusual situation.
You have to dump him
My God you have, like black, seen that he sends private pictures to her.
"But I love him" no he doesn't love you!
Brother.
Old man.
This is unfortunately ... I can't help you here.
This requires C.S.I.
This requires Fucking Private Investigator.
Firstly, why is your mom lying with your guy
Excuse me to make you uncomfortable but what is it that is going on here
Secondly, your guy can go to hell.
Thirdly, I don't know, I'm mute, I'm a puff.
The first time in my life but I am a puff.
We go on I got fucking darkened by that assism what sick people there are sometimes out in the world.
*Jack reads the problem*
*Anis reads the problem*
Why are all the dating issues Antonija?
Is that what the video is all about?
?
Your followers obviously have dating problems.
I also think this is a hard choice for him because he gets you and the children in a package, you understand what I mean then
*Anis reads the problem*
*Filip reads the problem*
*Jack reads the problem*
*Antonija reads the problem*
It will never be better between you, so sorry.
I have been in this situation where I met a girl who had been unfaithful before and a little such stuff.
And it's hard and I'm not saying he's right because he doesn't have it but it's hard.
So that here I think you have to make an effort if you really want to be with him to build trust.
You don't really have that commitment, but it can be good if you really want to be with him so to speak.
If he is so controlling then it will not be better between you.
If he wants to check who you spend time with, what you do, one and the other.
See you, goodbye, goodbye.
I'm not here to be a fucking robot that you fucking controls.
After all, you are not his property as it does not work this way.
This will be very busy for you if in is entering a relationship.
This will be going on for several years as I know, believe me, I know.
Leave him before it's too late, find a guy who can give you the love you deserve.
Point End Mother -Herpacker.
This guy has problems.
He got way to many issues.
You got to let him go.
Being jealous is a very bad and ugly trait, I am also a very jealous person.
And I think it is extremely difficult to be a jealous person as well.
And I definitely think you should talk to your dad that he doesn't ... So your dad shouldn't judge anyone for what someone has for a job or background.
Or what kind of culture or he has for religion.
Your dad should see the guy's qualities in that he wants you well.
I think that is extremely important and I think it's something you should talk to your dad about before you present this guy.
I think it can be very difficult with your dad but the only thing you can actually do is talk to your dad.
Introduce him, your dad gets to know your guy over time to see how amazing he is and that you love each other.
Your dad is a racist, we can start there.
I can't cope, your dad is a racist which is okay, it's not your fault that your dad is a racist.
But your dad is a racist if he sees your guy's culture as a problem or that the guy's culture would somehow limit the guy's opportunities for success.
Okay
Your father is a racist.
If you can't pay yourself, then you have to stand for it.
If you put your money on cigarettes and do not have money over and then do them wrong.
But if you know that you prioritize your cigarettes over something else which I understand, it can be difficult.
Then you can't join them in everything possible either and then expect them to pay just because you have problems with your smoking.
So I remember when I lived in Dubai.
Then there was a person who was with us who had a pretty small buffer.
I have always said so here you have to move abroad so have at least SEK 50,000 to your name.
In addition to travel money and stuff.
Because it may be that things are going.
And he wanted to come out and we would do stuff but he could never afford.
And then I said this to him: "The brother, I think it's a shame you can't keep up but you don't have the money, stay home.
"But I can't afford" and they may accept it.
If they can't accept it, they are probably no friends to have.
*Jasse reads the question*
Old man, then you just say we'll see you
Farewell, rubbish fits debris.
You should see this as a blessing from above.
Then God has shown .. brother, old man, brother
Sister, you are surrounded by junk.
You are naive, you do not understand that the people in your area are pathetic.
They are nasty so I'll give you a homework.
I'll show you that your closest people, your best friend and your guy .. is junk.
And I understand, what you go through now with your friend's dad is totally sick and nothing anyone should go through.
I don't know how good friends you are or if she knows about your situation.
But if it is that you are good friends and she knows what you have been through ..
And you tell her what is happening at her home with her disgusting fucking dad ..
Then she should grasp.
She might suppress it because she thinks "my dad is not like that".
Well your dad is a fucking disgust.
I get so annoyed, whose dad hangs on the tavern
With people who could be his children
It is very vast.
I do not know how far he has gone, but this can be reported to the police 100%.
Iom the situation you have been in when you were younger ..
Because this is already disgusting.
It's not okay for him to paw at you unless you want it.
And just there he has done something very disgusting.
I hadn't even wanted to know what could have happened if you were alone.
Do you understand what I mean
I had considered stopping spending time with this friend for a while anyway.
To remove me from this man.
So her father.
*Filip reads the question*
Congratulations
*Filip continues to read*
*Jasse continues to read*